▍2026 美网 男单1/4决赛
谢尔顿 6-7⁵ 6-1 6-3 1-6 7-6⁷ 阿尔卡拉斯 · 赛后场上采访
Ben, it's late.
本 已经很晚了
We'll try to make this quick,
我们尽量快一点
but I mean the question is just how How
但问题就是 怎么做到的？
did you do it?
你是怎么做到的？
How did you have the energy?
你哪来这样的体力？
How did you have the resolve
你哪来这样的决心
to do that in five sets?
撑下这场五盘大战？
You know for me For me,
对我来说 对我来说
it's always about the people
始终是因为现场的观众
in the crowd whether it's you know
看台上的每个人 无论是
My coaches and my team
我的教练和团队
over there all my family and friends
那边 还有我的家人朋友
over here Or the city of New York
这边 还有纽约这座城
that showed up tonight till 3 a.m.
今晚陪我们撑到凌晨三点
With the USA chants until the very end.
USA的呐喊一直响到最后
That's what kept me going
是你们让我坚持
and that's what got me
也帮我拿下
this win tonight Well you you know you set
今晚这场胜利 你创下了
a record.
一项纪录
It's past 3 a.m..
现在已经过了凌晨三点
This is way past the longest This has ever
这远超以往最晚的时间
been so what do you have to say
你想说些什么
to this crowd
对这些观众
that actually stayed here cheering for you?
他们一直留下来为你加油
I heard a lot of USA chants.
我听到阵阵USA的呼喊
I heard a lot of 'Go Ben!' Means
还有本 加油的呐喊
so much to them that you did this Yeah,
你赢了 意义重大 是啊
I mean, it's it's it's incredible.
这真的 真的太不可思议
I always say
我总说
that this is the greatest sports city
这里是最棒的体育之城
in the world I say
在全世界 我说
that this is the greatest stadium
这里是最棒的球场
in the world I'm just hoping
在全世界 我只希望
that my my best friend and my sister
我最好的朋友和我的姐妹
over there don't have to be at work
在那边 不用去上班
at 6 a.m.
早上六点
In three hours It'd be huge
也就是三小时后 那就太棒了
from their employers
要是他们的老板
to let them have the day off today,
能让他们今天放一天假
but No, I'm just I'm just so grateful
不过 我真的非常感激
so blessed God's blessed me
很有福气 上帝眷顾我
in so many ways to be here
在很多方面 让我来到这里
in front of you guys tonight It's
今晚 站在你们面前
an absolute honor sharing the court
同场竞技是莫大的荣幸
with Carlos is an absolute honor
和卡洛斯打球 是我的荣幸
and I cherish every moment
我珍惜每一刻
that I have out here Well,
在这里的每一刻 好了
you've got the day off tomorrow
你明天可以休息
and the next day enjoy it get
后天也能休息 好好享受
to the recovery You ladies
去做恢复 女士们
and gentlemen Ben Shelton
先生们 本·谢尔顿